Change your Mind. Change your Body. Change your Life.
Heal is a documentary film directed by Kelly Noonan.
A documentary film that takes us on a scientific and spiritual journey where we discover that
by changing one's perceptions, the human body can heal itself from any disease.
Self, played by Deepak Chopra.
Self, played by Marianne Williamson.
Self, played by Anita Moorjani.
Self, played by Bruce H. Lipton.
Self, played by Michael Beckwith.
Self, played by Gregg Braden.
Heal is a 2017 documentary film that was written and directed by Kelly
Noonan-Gores and produced by Richell Morrissey  and Adam Schomer.
The film focuses on mind–body interventions and follows several individuals who
used these techniques after being diagnosed with a fatal disease.
It was reviewed by critics as an "infomercial" that makes some valid points while  it
pretends to be based on science, yet some believe it promotes pseudoscience.
The film explores themes of yoga, health, spiritual, healing process, healing.